	{"QuestionBank":{

			"EasyBank":[

			    {
			    "QuestionID":"0000", 
			    "Question":" How do I store the value 1 to the variable x in python?",
			    "Answers":{
				    "CorrectAnswer": " x = 1", 
				    "Incorrect1": " x == 1", 
				    "Incorrect2": " int x == 1", 
				    "Incorrect3" : " 1 = x " 
				}
				},

				{
			    "QuestionID":"0001", 
			    "Question":" YOU know....?",
			    "Answers":{
				    "CorrectAnswer": " Frodo", 
				    "Incorrect1": " Odyseus", 
				    "Incorrect2": " motion ", 
				    "Incorrect3" : " c++ " 
				}
			    },

			    {
			    "QuestionID":"0002", 
			    "Question":" Easy question of all questions?",
			    "Answers":{
				    "CorrectAnswer": " BOOM!", 
				    "Incorrect1": " b explode bomb", 
				    "Incorrect2": " Pick ME! ", 
				    "Incorrect3" : " Sonny " 
				}
			    }

			    {
			    "QuestionID":"0003", 
			    "Question":" Easy question 003?",
			    "Answers":{
				    "CorrectAnswer": " this thingy!", 
				    "Incorrect1": " no", 
				    "Incorrect2": " no ", 
				    "Incorrect3" : " no " 
				}
			    }
			 	
			 	{
			    "QuestionID":"0004", 
			    "Question":" Easy question 004?",
			    "Answers":{
				    "CorrectAnswer": " this thingy!", 
				    "Incorrect1": " no", 
				    "Incorrect2": " no ", 
				    "Incorrect3" : " no " 
				}
			    }

			    {
			    "QuestionID":"0005", 
			    "Question":" Easy question 005?",
			    "Answers":{
				    "CorrectAnswer": " this thingy!", 
				    "Incorrect1": " no", 
				    "Incorrect2": " no ", 
				    "Incorrect3" : " no " 
				}
			    }
			],

			"MediumBank":[

				{
			    "QuestionID":"1000", 
			    "Question":" In Python, what is the command to display hello world to the standard output?",
			    "Answers":{
				    "CorrectAnswer": " print \"hello world\"", 
				    "Incorrect1": " console.log \"hello world\"", 
				    "Incorrect2": " cout << \"hello world\"", 
				    "Incorrect3" : " disp (\"hello world\")" 
				}
			    },

			    {
			    "QuestionID":"1001", 
			    "Question":" Which of the folowing returns 0?",
			    "Answers":{
				     "CorrectAnswer": " 0 if true else 1", 
				     "Incorrect1": " 1 if true else 0", 
				     "Incorrect2": " x = 0 ", 
				     "Incorrect3" : " if 0: 1 " 
				 }
			     },

			    {
			    "QuestionID":"1002", 
			    "Question":" Medium question of all questions?",
			    "Answers":{
				    "CorrectAnswer": " 42", 
				    "Incorrect1": " i can haz cheesburger", 
				    "Incorrect2": " F = ma ", 
				    "Incorrect3" : " Newtons 3rd law of motion " 
				}
			    }

			    {
			    "QuestionID":"1003", 
			    "Question":" Medium question 003?",
			    "Answers":{
				    "CorrectAnswer": " this thingy!", 
				    "Incorrect1": " no", 
				    "Incorrect2": " no ", 
				    "Incorrect3" : " no " 
				}
			    }

			    {
			    "QuestionID":"1004", 
			    "Question":" Medium question 004?",
			    "Answers":{
				    "CorrectAnswer": " this thingy!", 
				    "Incorrect1": " no", 
				    "Incorrect2": " no ", 
				    "Incorrect3" : " no " 
				}
			    }

			    {
			    "QuestionID":"1005", 
			    "Question":" Medium question 005?",
			    "Answers":{
				    "CorrectAnswer": " this thingy!", 
				    "Incorrect1": " no", 
				    "Incorrect2": " no ", 
				    "Incorrect3" : " no " 
				}
			    }
			],

			"HardBank":[

				{
			    "QuestionID":"2000", 
			    "Question":"which of the following will display the value of x and a descriptive string to the standard output if x is a string?",
			    "Answers":{
				     "CorrectAnswer": " print \"The value of x is: {}\".format(x) ", 
				     "Incorrect1": " print  \"The value of x is:\" + x ", 
				     "Incorrect2": " y = \"The value of x is: {}\".format(x)", 
				     "Incorrect3" : " y =  print  \"The value of x is:\" + xs" 
				 }
				 },

				{
			    "QuestionID":"2001", 
			    "Question":"Which of the following represents a conditional statement in python?",
			    "Answers":{
				     "CorrectAnswer": " if ( x == 3 )", 
				     "Incorrect1": " x = 2", 
				     "Incorrect2": " x == 2", 
				     "Incorrect3" : " print \"hello world\"" 
				}
			    },

			    {
			    "QuestionID":"2002", 
			    "Question":"Hard question of all questions?",
			    "Answers":{
				    "CorrectAnswer": " Cake!", 
				    "Incorrect1": " Cher", 
				    "Incorrect2": " PV = nRT ", 
				    "Incorrect3" : " PA = LU factorization " 
				}
			    }

			    {
			    "QuestionID":"2003", 
			    "Question":" Hard question 003?",
			    "Answers":{
				    "CorrectAnswer": " this thingy!", 
				    "Incorrect1": " no", 
				    "Incorrect2": " no ", 
				    "Incorrect3" : " no " 
				}
			    }

			    {
			    "QuestionID":"2004", 
			    "Question":" Hard question 004?",
			    "Answers":{
				    "CorrectAnswer": " this thingy!", 
				    "Incorrect1": " no", 
				    "Incorrect2": " no ", 
				    "Incorrect3" : " no " 
				}
			    }

			    {
			    "QuestionID":"2005", 
			    "Question":" Hard question 005?",
			    "Answers":{
				    "CorrectAnswer": " this thingy!", 
				    "Incorrect1": " no", 
				    "Incorrect2": " no ", 
				    "Incorrect3" : " no " 
				}
			    }
			]
		}
	}